Let's talk about it later.
What's wrong, Xingcan?
I was just discussing work with a colleague.
Let's leave work for tomorrow.
I need to head back now.
What happened?
The contract for that previous case
must be revised and sent back today.
I'm sorry, darling.
I'll spend time with you tomorrow, okay?
Okay, I'll drive you.
No need.
You're so tired today.
I'll just take a taxi back later.
Bye.
Chenyao.
Chenyao, wake up.
Don't scare me.
How is it?
Hold on a little longer.
Is Chenyao feeling better?
I'm
so hot.
I'll go get some ice.
Chenyao, Chenyao.
Wake up.
You said you still have an unfulfilled mission.
You can't leave me.
Please wake up.
Wake up.
Chenyao.
Chenyao, wake up.
Don't leave me. I beg you.
If you are in danger, blow this flute,
and I will appear.
You're awake.
You're so strong.
Chen Yao.
Can you stop scaring me?
Don't use your powers so easily from now on.
Do you hear me?
As you wish.
It was too dangerous this time.
You scared me to death.
What powers?
Mind your own business.
What exactly happened yesterday?
Why did Brother Chen become like this?
And,
why did I sleep holding the locksmith
on the stairs all night?
Stop asking.
From now on, when we carry out missions,
we must be extremely careful
to avoid this kind of danger.
It's fine. I just need a moment to recover.
No.
Do you just want to finish the mission quickly
and leave here?
No.
Brother Chen,
where are you going?
Anyway, you have to follow my orders in future missions.
You too.
Okay.
It should be the delivery. You feed him.
We only have this one chance.
Let's split up now.
I'll go to Lingze's house first
to stall them.
Take this opportunity.
Chen Yao,
go to the study in Lingze's house and open the safe.
Hurry up and set up surveillance in Lingze's office, the live broadcast room,
and the company entrance
to cover all of Lingze's movements.
There can't be any mistakes.
Lure them into a trap.
We're counting on this to bring them down.
My hands are full.
Hello.
Xingcan.
Father has already arranged
the date of our wedding.
I've made an appointment at the bridal shop.
Come and try it on tomorrow.
Okay.
Since staying by his side is so painful,
why don't we
change our plan?
I can do it no matter how many times we start over.
This time is the smoothest and most effective one.
I can do it.
All right, I'll stay with you.
What are you doing?
Why would a spirit drink alcohol?
Alcohol is very expensive, okay?
I'll drink with you.
Just eat some ice cubes.
I don't need your company.
Fine.
Hey.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Chen Yao.
Come have a drink with me.
I don't drink.
Just have a couple of drinks with me.
Why would a fairy drink?
And your wine is so expensive.
Petty.
Then let's play a game instead of drinking.
No.
Let's play.
I know I'm always being unreasonable.
I'm really unhappy today.
I don't even know how to vent.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have made such an unreasonable request.
I'll try my best to be what my dad wants,
a sensible and independent child.
Don't say that.
I won't cause you any more trouble.
You've never been a bother to me.
Fine, I'll play with you.
Okay.
Whoever laughs first loses.
You laughed.
No, I didn't.
Why do I always lose?
I'm not playing with you anymore.
Are you a block of ice? No feelings at all.
You laughed.
I haven't even started yet.
We started.
You didn't say start.
Let me flick you.
I didn't lose. Why should I let you flick me?
You just laughed.
You can't cheat.
No, I didn't.
You.
You definitely laughed just now.
Are you okay?
You... you cheated.
I bounced it back.
We can still try other ways.
No matter how many times we try,
as long as I'm here, it's fine.
No.
I can't risk your body anymore.
We've come this far.
Almost there.
For you,
I don't mind.
Xingcan.
This is the scene I've dreamed of the most.
You are so beautiful.
You,
take the best clothes in your store
and bring them all out.
Okay, Mr. Ling.
Let her try them on one by one
until she is satisfied. Okay.
Okay.